<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Corespirit</string>
    <string name="articles">Articles</string>
    <string name="reloadLoadScreenButton">Reload</string>
    <string name="on_network_error">Network error! Please, reload app</string>
    <string name="articleAuthor">By: </string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forget password?</string>
    <string name="submitCredentials">Submit</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="enter_login">Enter login</string>
    <string name="notFound">woops! Nothing found :(</string>
    <string name="default_practitioner_name">Name hidden</string>
    <string name="about_us_title">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="about_us_content"><![CDATA[CORE SPIRIT is a movement aspiring to raise the collective consciousness and enhance the human race, a possibility to get better in every aspect of life for the humanity on all levels: Individual, Family, Society, Humanity, Earth, Universe &amp; God. CS is the only online platform combining knowledge about wellness of the body, power of the mind, wholeness of spirituality, achieving life balance and in addition, rich with uncompromising supportive scientific research.</p><p class=\"MuiTypography-root jss254 MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">CS initially kickstarted as an aggregator with the intention to consolidate knowledge further on started generating more content to expand knowledge within its targeted subject matter.</p><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">CORE SPIRIT’s knowledge and services help find balance, harmony and drive towards a more enlightened life with a clearer vision and less fearful thoughts by finding mentors, following outstanding people, joining different practices and meeting a like-minded audience. CS platform combines possibilities for both practitioners and those willing to open up and improve their lives – practitioners write articles in their field of expertise for the whole community to read. CS hosts a radio channel and CS Tube for videos where the deepest topics are discussed.</p><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">Educational events regularly take place on CS in the form of both online and offline conferences, workshops and courses. Every practitioner can organize their own event and every visitor can choose one to visit. A vast marketplace holds a store to buy and sell the needed tools for unique practices. Apart from that, practitioners organize, and seekers visit online or offline healing sessions and consultancy. For practitioners only, there is an Entrepreneurial Mentor, a valuable aid for promoting your services and making your name known.</p><p class=\"MuiTypography-root jss250 MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">We believe that with an open heart and mind one can step on the road to enlightenment and reach serenity.</p></section><section><h3 class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">Our Story to Date</h3><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">The story of CORE SPIRIT started in 2014 when a group of enthusiasts interested in full enhancement of human life, took up a hobby – writing and enlightening people as well as uniting like-minded individuals to share their unique knowledge. To CS founders own surprise, response was so vast and instant that it became clear — the platform had to grow to meet the needs of thousands of seekers. People were coming to CS from all over the world regardless of their gender, age, race, nationality, religious and cultural background.</p><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">This is how the idea was confirmed that the topic is fascinating and beneficial for many people and a platform like this can give a lot to the whole humanity. CS became not just a hobby but a profession when the founders started to think the platform through to the smallest details and came up with its integral parts — articles, events, market place and Entrepreneurial Mentor.</p><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">Today, CS is actively building up its audience from all over the world coming to learn about different practices and to start living to the fullest – with an open heart and mind. CS already has a very strong base of practitioners that will only expand, and new categories will be added.</p><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">The founders regard ethics and moral norms as of paramount importance of CS that stays free from politics, discrimination and judgement.</p></section><section><h3 class=\"MuiTypography-root jss258 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">Components of CS</h3><h4 class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">Practitioners</h4><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">Practitioners are those people who have reached enlightenment and who are ready to share their knowledge with the rest of us. On CS, practitioners write articles in the field of their expertise, organize events and private sessions and upgrade their skills by expanding their practice.</p><h4 class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">Users</h4><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">Users are those eager to learn and enhance their life on all levels by receiving invaluable knowledge from practitioners, visiting educational events and personal healing sessions. On CS, users can find an answer to any of their questions — whether it concerns their body of the Spirit.</p><h4 class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">Marketplace</h4><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">Marketplace is where users can find additional tools for a complete experience as they start a particular practice and practitioners can sell their books or anything else they believe can be helpful for a better experience.</p><h4 class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">Entrepreneurial Mentor</h4><p class=\"MuiTypography-root jss254 MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">Entrepreneurial Mentor is a valuable tool for practitioners to help their practice growand learn how to reach large audience. E-Mentor identifies practitioner’s level and sets the focus as well as specific business goals providing analytics along the way. It’s a helpful friend that allows practitioners focus on their practices and gives an opportunity to expand their business along the way.</p><h4 class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">Education</h4><p class=\"MuiTypography-root jss254 MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\">Regardless of whether you are a practitioner or a user, already know a lot about different practices or just starting to learn – CS is a platform for you to keep on growing as you read articles, meet outstanding people and visit events organized byyour colleagues or your role models.</p></section><section><h3 class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom\">When will this all happen?</h3><p class=\"MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph\"><span class=\"jss248 jss251 jss258\">Right now! CS is growing rapidly so subscribe to catch every opportunity.</span></p></section></div></div></div></div></main>]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_title">PRIVACY POLICY</string>
    <string name="privacy_content"><![CDATA[PRIVACY POLICY</h2><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">Core Spirit is committed to maintaining robust privacy protection for its users. Our Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Site. For purposes of this Agreement, “Site” refers to www.corespirit.com. The terms “we”, “us”and “our” refer to Core Spirit. “You” refers to you, as a user of the Site or the Service. By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">The founders regard ethics and moral norms as of paramount importance of CS that stays free from politics, discrimination and judgement.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">II. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">Personal Information: Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade,rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for Core Spirit, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user’s email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Those vendors use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">In general, the Personal Information you provide may be used in one of the following ways:</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to yourindividual needs)</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you)</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">Non-Personal Information: In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Service and customize the user experience. We also may aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">III. DISCLOSING YOUR INFORMATION</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or providing services to you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We also may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">IV. YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional email.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">V. YOUR CONTENT</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">VI. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">Core Spirit reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time. We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your email registration. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">VII. CONTACT US</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please don’t hesitate to contact us by sending an email to info@corespirit.com]]></string>
    <string name="terms_title">TERMS OF SERVICE</string>
    <string name="terms_content"><![CDATA[TERMS OF SERVICE</h2><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">These terms and conditions govern your use of our website. Please read the terms in full before you use this website. If you do not accept these terms, please do not use this website. Using the site implies that you accept these terms. We do occasionally update these terms, so please refer back to them in the future.</p><h3 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h3 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">LEGAL</h3><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">Core Spirit respects the privacy of its Users. Please refer to Core Spirit’s Privacy Policy, which explains how we collect, use and disclose information that pertains to your privacy.</p><h4 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">1. SITE ACCESS</h4><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">You will be able to access this website without having to register any details with us.</p><h4 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">2. USE OF WEBSITE</h4><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">You are permitted to use our website for your own purposes and to print and download material from this website provided that you do not modify any content without our consent. Material on this website must not be republished online or offline without our permission.</p><h4 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">3. VISITOR CONDUCT</h4><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">With the exception of personally identifiable information, the use of which is covered under ourPrivacy Policy, any material you send or post to this website shall be considered non-proprietary and not confidential. Unless you advise to the contrary, we will be free to copy, disclose,distribute, incorporate and otherwise use such material for any and all purposes.</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">When using this website, you shall not post or send to or from this website any material:</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">-for which you have not obtained all necessary consents;</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">-that is discriminatory, obscene, pornographic, defamatory, liable to incite racial hatred, in breach of confidentiality or privacy, which may cause annoyance or inconvenience to others, which encourages or constitutes conduct that would be deemed a criminal offense, give rise to a civil liability or otherwise is contrary to the law;</p><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">-which is harmful in nature including, and without limitation, computer viruses, Trojan horses, corrupted data or other potentially harmful software or data.</p><h4 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">4. LINKS TO AND FROM OTHER SITES</h4><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">Any links to third party websites located on this website are provided for your convenience only. We have not reviewed each third party website and have no responsibility for such third party websites or their content. We do not endorse the third party websites or make represent actions about them or any material contained in them. If you choose to access a third party website linked to from this website, it is at your own risk.</p><h4 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">5. DISCLAIMER</h4><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">We take all reasonable steps to ensure that the information on this website is correct. However,we do not guarantee the correctness or completeness of material on this website. We may make changes to the material on this website at any time and without notice. The material on this website may be out of date or, on rare occasions, incorrect, and we make no commitment to ensure that such material is correct or up to date. The material on this website is provided without any conditions or warranties of any kind. To the maximum extent permitted by law, we provide access and use of this website on the basis that we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions, which but for these Terms may have effect in relation to this website.</p><h4 class="MuiTypography-root jss252 jss259 MuiTypography-h4 MuiTypography-gutterBottom">6. EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY</h4><p class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 MuiTypography-paragraph">Neither we nor any other party (whether or not involved in producing, maintaining or delivering this website), shall be liability or responsible for any kind of loss or damage that may result to you or a third party as a result of your or their use of our website. This exclusion shall include servicing or repair costs and, without limitation, any other direct, indirect or consequential loss, and whether in tort or contract or otherwise in connection with this website. Nothing in these Terms shall exclude or limit liability for; or (iv) any liability, which cannot be excluded or limited under the law.</p>]]></string>
</resources>
